A Guide to the Charles E. Culpeper Foundation, Inc. records FA025
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 1, 1866-1998; 1; 32 Cubic Feet
  - Grants, 1969-1990; 2; 5.2 Cubic Feet
    - Grants, 1969-1987; 1
      - Carr-Colu, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
        Carroll College, 1979 Carver Foundation of Norwalk, Inc., 1974 Casita Maria, Inc., 1969 Catholic Near East Welfare Foundation, Inc., 1976 Catholic Relief Services, 1970 Centenary College, 1983 The Center for the Environment and Man, Inc., 1979 Center for the Hudson River Valley, 1977 Central Naugatuck Valley Mental Health Council, Inc. Central Park Conservancy, 1981 Champion Center, 1975 Charter Oak Temple, 1982 Childrens Aid Society, 1977 Childrens Medical Relief International, Inc., 1971 Childrens Memorial Hospital, 1980 Church of St. Phillip and St. James, 1978 Church of the Ascension, 1978 Clifford W. Beers Guidance Clinic, Inc., 1979 College of Physicians of Philadelphia, 1983 Columbia University College of Physicians and Surgions, 1978
      - Con-Dan, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
        The Connecticut Grand Opera, 1980 Connecticut Hospice, Inc., 1983 Connecticut Humane Society, 1969 Connecticut Nautilus Committee, 1983 Council on Learning, 1983 Culver-Stockton College, 1982 Danbury Association to Advance the Handicapped and Retarded, 1973 Danbury Hospital, 1976
      - Devereux Foundation, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
      - Dow-For, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
        Downtown Talmud Torah, 1969 The Dublin Community Church, 1978 Early Learning Center, Inc., 1978 East Harlem Tutorial Program, 1979 Environmental Defense Fund, 1973 Environmental Law Center - Vermont Law School, 1974 Episcopal Housing Operation, 1973 Eugene O'Neill Theater Center, 1980 Eye Bank for Sight Restoration, Inc., 1978 Fairfield County Council #68 Boy Scouts of America, 1973 Faith Hospital, 1983 Family & Children Services, 1969 Floating Hospital, 1972 Florida Institute of Technology, 1973 Foresight, Inc., 1979
      - Fou-Gro, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
        Foundation for Vascular Hypertension Research, 1978 The Foundation School, 1972 Gengras Center for Exceptional Children, 1981 Georgetown Preparatory School, 1978 Girls Club of New York, 1979 Goodwill Industries of Greater New York, Inc., 1971 Greenwich Association for Retarded Citizens, 1987 Grosvenor Neighborhood House, Inc., 1981
      - Had-Hop, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
        Hadley Memorial Hospital, 1979 The Hadley School for the Blind, 1976 Hamilton-Madison House, 1977 The Hammer School, 1976 Hastings Center, 1981 Harvard Medical School, 1977 Haskell Indian Junior College, 1978 Historic Fredricksburg Foundation, Inc., 1978 Holy Family Home for the Aged, 1969 Holy Trinity Church, 1978 Hopefields School Inc., Riverview School, 1983
      - How-Ins, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
        Howard University, 1976 House Ear Institute (Ear Research Institute), 1976 The Hudson Guild, 1971 Humane Society of Greater Miami, Inc., 1969 The Industrial Home for the Blind, 1971 Innovation Design Fund, Inc., 1983 The Institute for Architecture and Urban Studies, 1978 The Institute for Congress, 1976 Institute for Court Management, 1981 Institute for Public Interest Representation, 1974 Institute of Judicial Administration, 1981 Institute of Rehabilitative Medicine, 1971
      - Inte-Marc, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
        International Center for the Disabled, 1982 The International Oceanographic Foundation, 1973 International Society for Heart Research, 1983 Ithaca College, 1977 The Izaac Walton League of America, 1969 Jewish Board of Guardians, 1976 Joffrey Ballet, 1981 John Marshall House, 1974 John Muir Institute for Environmental Studies, 1976 John Tracy Clinic, 1977 Junior Sea Knights of America, Inc., 1973 Kennebac Girl Scout Council, 1973 Keystone House Inc., 1973 Leader Dogs for the Blind, 1969 The Learning Center for Deaf Children, 1971 Lenox Hill Neighborhood Association, Inc., 1971 Lion Libraries on Line, Inc., 1982 Little Sisters of the Poor, 1974 Lutheran Braille Workers Inc., 1969 Lutheran Medical Center, 1974 Maplebrook School, 1971 March of Dimes Birth Defects Foundation, 1980
      - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - Marq-National (G), undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
        Marquette University, 1978 Mary Manning Walsh Home, 1972 The Matheny School, 1980 Mayor's Voluntary Action Center, 1983 Medical College of Philadelphia and Hospital, 1982 Medical Mission Sisters, 1973 Meharry Medical College, 1978 Mercy Hospital, 1969 Methodist Church Home for the Aged, 1980 Miami Heart Institute, 1969 Miami Multiple Sclerosis Association, 1969 Miami Rescue Mission of the Miami Mission Association, 1969 Mianus River Gorge Conservation Committee (Nature Conservancy), 1974 Middlesex Memorial Hospital, 1978 Milton S. Hershey Medical Center, 1982 Montefiore Hospital and Medical Center, 1979 Morality in Media, 1971 (More House) St. Thomas More House, 1976 Mount Sinai Medical Center, 1982 The Mountainside Hospital, 1969 Mullen Home for the Elderly, 1976 Municipal Art Society of New York, 1978 Nantucket Defense Fund, 1977 The Nassau Center for Emotionally Disturbed Children, 1973 National Geographic Society, 1969
      - National Information Bureau, Inc., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - National (M)-Oc, undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
        National Medical Fellowships, Inc., 1971 National Parks Association, 1969 National Science for Youth Foundation, Inc., 1971 National Shrine of the Immaculate Conception, 1980 National Wildlife Federation, 1969 The Nature Conservancy, 1969 Navajo Community College, 1970 Navy Yard Boys Club, 1975 New Canaan Country School, 1978 New England Congressional Institute, 1982 New Rochelle Hospital Medical Center, 1979 New York Association for the Blind, 1977 New York City Ballet, 1978 The New York Community Trust, 1980 New York Infirmary, 1974 New York League for the Hard of Hearing, 1969 New York Ocean Science Laboratory of Affiliated Colleges and Universities, 1975 The New York Times Neediest Cases Fund, 1970 New York University Medical Center, 1976 Noreen McKeen Residence for Geriatric Care, 1983 North Carolina School of the Arts Foundation, INC., 1981 Norwalk Association for the Blind, Inc.,1977 Norwalk Day Nursery Association, Inc., 1972 The Norwalk Hospital, 1969 Norwalk Jewish Community Center, 1975 Norwalk YMCA, 1971 The Oceanic Institute, 1975 The Oceanic Society, 1977
      - Ol-Saint (Lab), undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
        Old Globe Theatre, 1981 Omega Ensemble, 1980 Opera America, Inc., 1983 Oregon Commission of the Judicial Branch, 1981 Pacific Union College, 1983 Park East Eshi Day School (formerly East Side Hebrew Institute), 1970 Partnership for the Homeless, 1983 Pembroke State University, 1981 Phoenix Science Center, 1978 Pope John II Center for Health Care, 1983 Preparatory Premedical Research and Education Program, 1978 Project Concern International, 1980 The Queens Medical Center (Honolulu, Hawaii), 1979 Red Cloud Indian School, 1969 Rehabilitation Center of Southwestern Connecticut, Inc. (Fairfield County, Inc.), 1979 Roosevelt Hospital, 1970 Saint Augustine's College, 1975 Saint Barnabus Hospital for Chronic Diseases, 1969 Saint Christopher's - Jennie Clarkson Child, 1975 Saint Clare's Hospital and Health Center, 1977 Saint Edwards Reading Center (The Church of Saint Edward the Martyr), 1975 Saint Josephs Manor, 1969 Saint Labre Indian School, 1969
      - Saint (Law)-Sal, undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
        Saint Lawrence University, 1974 Saint Louis Children's Hospital, 1981 Saint Lukes Chamber Ensemble, Inc., 1979 Saint Margarets Hospital for Women, 1981 Saint Mark's Church in the Bowery, 1979 Saint Michaels Association for Special Education, 1977 Saint Michael's Farm for Boys, 1976 Saint Peter's College, 1969 Saint Thomas Church, 1980 Saint Thomas More Parish, 1980 Saint Vincent's Hospital and Medical Center of New York, 1972 Salvation Army, 1969
      - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, Inc., 1981 (Box 3, Folder 19)
      - Sam-Str, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
        Samaritan Health Service, 1978 Save the Children Federation, Inc., 1969 School of the Holy Child, 1973 School of the Ozarks, 1975 Search and Care, 1975 Services to the Blind, Inc., 1975 Shaker Community, Inc., 1976 Shorter College, 1976 Silvermine Guild of Artists, Inc., 1971 Sisters of the Blessed Sacrament, 1972 Sisters of Saint Thomas of Villanova, 1973 Smith College, 1977 Society of the Holy Child Jesus, 1976 So Others May Eat, 1979 Society for the Rehabilitation for the Facially Disfigured, Inc., 1978 South Kent School, 1978 South Jersey Wetlands Institute, 1971 South Queens Boy's Club, Inc., 1975 Southwest Indian Foundation, 1969 Southwestern University School Of Law, 1977 The Sports Foundation, Inc., 1980 The Stamford Foundation, 1980 The Stamford Hospital, 1969 State of Maine Judicial Court, 1978 Stonehill College, 1980 The Stowe School, 1978 Strang Clinic - Preventive Medicine Institute, 1977
      - Su-Tr, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
        Suffield Academy, 1983 Texas Tech University, 1981 Theatre in a Trunk, Inc., 1978 Transfiguration of Christ Greek Orthodox School, 1969 Trinity Episcopal Church, 1978
      - Tur-Vin, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
        Turtle Bay Music School, Inc., 1979 Union League of Southwestern Fairfield County, Inc., 1974 United Methodist Convalescent Home of Connecticut, Inc., 1969 United States Association for Blind Athletes, 1982 United States Catholic Conference, Inc., 1971 United Way of Norwalk (Society to Advance the Retarded), 1975 University of Cincinnati, 1980 University of Missouri Columbia School of Veterinary Medicine, 1972 University of New Hampshire, 1978 University of Richmond, 1977 University of Tulsa, 1979 Upper Raritan Watershed Association, 1973 USS Constitution Museum, 1982 Variety Childrens Hospital, 1969 Vincent T. Lombardi Cancer Research Center - Georgetown Medical Center, 1977
      - Vit-Zoo, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
        Vitam Center, Inc., 1983 Wake Forest University, Bowman Gray School of Medicine, 1980 Washburn University of Topeka, 1977 Washington College, 1973 Waterbury Association for Retarded Children, Inc., 1969 Waveny Care Center, 1977 Webb-Waring Institute, 1977 The Wetlands Institute (South Jersey Wetlands Institute), 1973 Wilton YMCA, 1983 Woods Hole Oceanographic Institute, 1969 World Research, Inc., 1973 World Wildlife Fund, 1969 YMCA of Bridgeport, 1981 YMCA of Greater New Haven, 1978 YMCA of Greater New York, 1977 YMCA of Stamford (Junior League of South Norwalk, Inc.), 1973 Young Women's Christian Association of Brooklin, 1974 Zoological Society of Florida, 1969
    - Medical Research Program, 1977-1987; 2
      - A-J, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
        Albert Einstein College of Medicine - David Hamerman, 1986 Dartmouth Medical School - Jay Dunlap, 1985 Jefferson Medical College - Michael Moritz, 1986
      - Massachusetts (G-I), undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
        Massachusetts General Hospital/Harvard Medical School - Marek Skoskiewicz, 1982 Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Robert Lees, 1977
      - Massachusetts (I)-Mi, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
        Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Susumu Tonegawa, 1982 Michigan Molecular Institute - Susan Hawkes, 1983
      - New York Hospital/Cornell Medical Center, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 27)
        Betty Danes
      - New York (M-U), undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
        New York Medical College - Robert Browner, 1984 New York University Medical Center - Jean-Claude Bystryn, 1987
      - New York University Medical Center/Institute of Rehabilitation Medicine, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 29)
        Leonard Diller
      - Research Applications, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Research Grants Pending, 1984-1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Research Logs (A-Z), undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Research Proposals Reviewed/Rejected, undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - University of Akron, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 34)
        Ronald Viola
      - University of California, 1983-1985 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - University of California, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 36)
        Maria Lorenzi
      - University (D-M), undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
        University of Denver - Roger Clark, 1983 University of Michigan - Dorothy Coons, 1985 University of Minnesota - Pi-nian Chang, 1984-1985
      - University of Rochester, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 38)
        George Segel
      - University of Virginia, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 39)
        Robert Wenzel
      - University of Virginia, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 40)
        George Gillies
      - University of Virginia, 1987 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - V-W, undated (Box 6, Folder 42)
        Virginia Tech - Klaus Elgert, 1984 Washington State University - Michael Smerdon, 1983 Washington State University - Martin Pall, 1984
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 43)
        Laura Ment
    - Medical Sciences Fellowships, 1979-1989; 3
      - Approval of Schools for Fellowships - Correspondence with Dr. Glenn re: Fellowships, undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Boston University School of Medicine, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 45)
        Glenn Allison Ronald Ellis David Fahey Karla Kanis Jerome Myers Ben Philosophe William Quist
      - Boston University School of Medicine, 1987-1988 (Box 7, Folder 46)
        Peter Angelos Peter Crino Thomas Crisman Daniel Kohane Peter Mogayzel Timothy O'Hare Johndavid Pollack James Pomposelli
      - Boston University School of Medicine, 1988-1989 (Box 7, Folder 47)
        Fredrick Hing Ken Lin David Mischoulon Kenton Schwartz Ira Skolnik Jason Sohet Steven Treon
      - University of Buffalo School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 48)
        Carlos Palant
      - University of Buffalo School of Medicine, 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 49)
        Tetsuri Kondo
      - University of California School of Medicine, 1982-1984 (Box 7, Folder 50)
        David Cox
      - University of California School of Medicine, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 51)
        Carl Mendel
      - University of California School of Medicine, 1986-1987 (Box 7, Folder 52)
        Michelle Capdelle Iris Cheng
      - University of Chicago School of Medicine, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 53)
        Beverly Ketel
      - University of Chicago School of Medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 54)
        C. Harold Yang
      - University of Chicago School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 55)
        Deborah Manjoney
      - University of Chicago School of Medicine, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 56)
        Myriam Curet-Scott
      - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 57)
        Leo Herbette
      - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1985-1986 (Box 8, Folder 58)
        Steven Padula
      - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1986-1987 (Box 8, Folder 59)
        Lynn Cates
      - University of Connecticut Health Center, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 60)
        Michael Gerber
      - Correspondence with Mr. Campbell Regarding Fellowship, undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
      - Duke University Medical School, 1981-1983 (Box 8, Folder 62)
        Augustus Grant
      - Duke University Medical School, 1983-1985 (Box 8, Folder 63)
        Y. T. Chen
      - East Carolina University School of Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 64)
        Robert Deepe
      - East Carolina University School of Medicine, 1981-1982 (Box 8, Folder 65)
        David Gordon
      - East Carolina University School of Medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 66)
        Beth Foil
      - East Carolina University School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 67)
        Dale Williams
      - Medical Sciences Fellowship Guidelines, undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
      - Harvard University, 1985-1987 (Box 8, Folder 69)
        Bruce Bean
      - Jefferson Medical College, 1980-1982 (Box 8, Folder 70)
        Clara Callahan
      - Jefferson Medical College, 1982-1983 (Box 8, Folder 71)
        Richard Fruncillo
      - Jefferson Medical College, 1983-1984 (Box 8, Folder 72)
        Lawrence Brent
      - Mayo Graduate School of Medicine, 1984-1985 (Box 8, Folder 73)
        Lewis Essandoh
      - Mayo Graduate School of Medicine, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 74)
        April Chang-Miller
      - Mayo Graduate School of Medicine, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 75)
        Wayne Miller
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 76)
        Jeffrey Ravetch
      - Memorial Sloan-Kettering, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 77)
        Samuel Rabkin
      - University of North Carolina, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 78)
        Jon Woods
      - University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 79)
        Donald Dafoe
      - University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 80)
        James Hoxie
      - University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 81)
        Bryan Mandell
      - University of Pennsylvania Medical Center, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 82)
        Mark Ratcliff
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 83)
        Stephen Garlow Michael Harris Charles Lassman Allan Ramaley
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 84)
        Judith Badner Michael Harris Charles Lassman G. Scott Long
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 85)
        Judith Badner Scott Berceli Chuang Chuang Robert Nahouraii
      - University of Pittsburgh, 1988-1986 (Box 9, Folder 86)
        Nadhia Akhtar Scott Berceli Chuang Chuang Jacob Gordon
      - University of South Carolina, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 87)
        Alvin Fox
      - University of South Carolina, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 88)
        Katryna Bogovich
      - University of South Carolina, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 89)
        Philip Watson
      - University of South Carolina, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 90)
        William Moore
      - Status of All Fellowships, undated (Box 9, Folder 91)
      - St. Louis University, 1984-1986 (Box 9, Folder 92)
        Joseph Hoffman
      - St. Louis University, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 93)
        Thomas Olsen
      - St. Louis University, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 94)
        Mark Kline
      - Tulane University School of Medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 95)
        Marion Walters
      - Tulane University School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 96)
        Miriam Blitzer
      - Tulane University School of Medicine, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 97)
        Nancy Wang
      - University of Vermont School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 98)
        Lawrence Kromer
      - University of Vermont School of Medicine, 1984-1985 (Box 10, Folder 99)
        Carson Cornbrooks Jerome Fiekers
      - University of Vermont School of Medicine, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 100)
        David Warshaw
      - University of Vermont School of Medicine, 1986-1987 (Box 10, Folder 101)
        Charles Chambers Anne Hodgson William Roberts
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1979-1980 (Box 10, Folder 102)
        William Merrill
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 103)
        Michael Lerner
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 104)
        Anne Lucky
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 105)
        John Rankin
      - Yale University School of Medicine, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 106)
        Francis Collins
    - Social Sciences Fellowships, 1979-1986; 4
      - Brown University, undated (Box 11, Folder 107)
        Merilee Grindle, 1981-1982 Mark Lichbach, 1980-1981 Paul Peretz, 1983-1984
      - Dartmouth College, undated (Box 11, Folder 108)
        Steven Forde, 1983-1984 Ted Mitchell, 1980-1981 LeRoy Smith, 1982-1983
      - Social Sciences Fellowships Guidelines, undated (Box 11, Folder 109)
      - Oberlin College, undated (Box 11, Folder 110)
        John Patrick Dale, 1985-1986 Lois Helmbold, 1984-1985 Lily Hoffman, 1982-1983 Lloyd Orr, 1983-1984
      - Rice University, undated (Box 11, Folder 111)
        Joseph Stewart, 1981-1983
      - Rice University, undated (Box 11, Folder 112)
      - Rice University, undated (Box 11, Folder 113)
        Brian Klugar, 1983-1985
      - Smith College, undated (Box 11, Folder 114)
        Samuel Baker, 1981-1982 Donald Joralemon, 1983-1985 Victoria Joralemon, 1984-1985 Sharon Watson, 1982-1983
      - Wesleyan University, undated (Box 11, Folder 115)
        Joseph Carens, 1979-1984 Philip Clark, 1980-1981 Anne Marie Foltz, 1984-1985 Richard Hartwig, 1981-1982 Beverly Klimkowski, 1983-1984
      - Williams College, undated (Box 11, Folder 116)
        John Burke, 1982-1984 Helen Siu, 1980-1982
    - Visiting Professorships, 1980-1990; 5
      - Baylor College of Medicine, undated (Box 12, Folder 117)
        Francis Ruddle, 1983 Daniel Shannon, 1984
      - Boston University Medical Center, undated (Box 12, Folder 118)
        Robert Oldham, 1981 Robert Stepto, 1985
      - Boston University Medical Center, undated (Box 12, Folder 119)
        R. Scott Jones, 1982 Wendell Rosse, 1983 Michael Rutter, 1984
      - D-H, undated (Box 12, Folder 120)
        Dartmouth Medical School Robert Hockelman, 1984 Philip Rubin, 1985
        Emory University School of Medicine
        Guidelines
        Howard University College of Medicine Samuel Katz, 1985 Thomas Starzi, 1984
      - L-M, undated (Box 12, Folder 121)
        Louisiana State University Medical Center Mary Ellen Avery, 1985 L. H. Blumgart, 1984 Milton Elkin, 1981 F. Clark Fraser, 1982 Jesse Roth, 1983
        Meharry Medical College Melvin Jenkins, 1986 Clifford Leftridge, 1985
        University of Miami School of Medicine Brian Hoffman, 1985
      - Morehouse College School of Medicine, undated (Box 12, Folder 122)
        William Paul, 1981
      - N-Stan, undated (Box 12, Folder 123)
        New York University School of Medicine John Dietshg, 1983 Michael Parkhouse, 1985 Nicholas Zervas, 1984
        Oregon Health Sciences University, School of Medicine John Glover, 1984 Martha Howe, 1987 Rodney Million, 1986 Samuel Their, 1988 Raymond White, 1985
        Stanford University Medical Center Stanley Cohen, 1985 Saul Faber, 1981 William Hazzard, 1984 Madlyn McCarty, 1983 Rodney Million, 1982 Beatrice Mintz, 1983 Theodore Sherrod, 1982 Arnold Smith, 1984 Dean Warren, 1980
      - Stat-University (C), undated (Box 13, Folder 124)
        State University of New York at Stony Brook Michael Bishop, 1983 Herman Eisen, 1980 J. C. Goligher, 1982 John Laws, 1984 Philip Sunshine, 1981
        University of Arizona Health Sciences Center Robert Freeark, 1985 Elizabeth Hay, 1987 Saul Krugman, 1984 Elliott Lasser, 1986 J. Ledingham, 1983
        University of California at San Diego K. Frank Austen, 1986 Charles Higgens, 1987 Sidney Hurwetz, 1985 Geoffrey Spaney, 1984
      - University (F-Il), undated (Box 13, Folder 125)
        University of Florida
        University of Hawaii
        University of Illinois College of Medicine Mary Ellen Avery, 1982 Michael Capp, 1985 James Darnell, 1983 Norton Greenberger, 1984 Terrence Kennedy, 1981
      - University (Io-Ma), undated (Box 13, Folder 126)
        University of Iowa College of Medicine Herbert Abrams, 1981 Roy Calne, 1982 Max Cooper, 1983 Andrea Prader, 1980 Bergt Samuelson, 1984
        University of Kansas K. Frank Austen, 1985 Kurt Isselbacher, 1986 Michael Smith, 1987
        University of Massachusetts Eugene Robin, 1986 Donald Seldin, 1985
      - University (Mic-Neb), undated (Box 13, Folder 127)
        University of Michigan Medical School Eugene Braunwald, 1983 William Paul, 1982 Theodore Phillips, 1984 Henry Pitt, 1985 Larry Shapiro, 1986
        University of Mississippi Medical Center Charles Cummings, 1986 John Harris, 1982 Frank Oski, 1983 David Rimoin, 1984 Lloyd Smith, 1985
        University of Nebraska Medical Center Noel Rose, 1985 Gerold Schiebler, 1986 William Kelley, 1984 Thomas Lawson, 1982 Dean Warren, 1983